wireclub.com 2007-12-10

# WireClub.com - Free Chat, Dating, Friends & More

### Privacy Statement

WireClub.com is continually committed to your privacy by both safeguarding your personal information and enforcing a strict policy of non-disclosure to third parties. Any updates to this document will be emailed to all registered users who have not opted out of email communication. 

### Information automatically collected from visitors:

We use your computer’s IP address (a unique number used to identify your computer on the internet) to maintain statistics and to identify potential problems. Your IP address is not tied to your personal information in any way and can not be used to identify you. 

WireClub.com also uses a cookie (a small file stored on your machine) to identify users once they have logged in and to optionally save their password if they choose to. This use of cookies is very common on the internet and is required to avoid having to log in to every page you want to access. 

### Personal information provided by members:

All personal information submitted as part of the registration process is kept in our secure database and never disclosed to third parties. Any information that is entered as part of a public profile will be available to all visitors to the website but will never be given to third parties as a bulk operation. We enforce our user’s right to privacy and never publicize fields that are marked as private such as your real name. Any field that has an opt-out option such as ‘prefer not to say’ is up to the user to provide and will not deny access to any part of the site.
